<ORGANIZATION>Richmond & Danville Railroad</ORGANIZATION>.
Fourth of <DATE>July</DATE> Excursion to <LOCATION>Amelia Springs</LOCATION>.
Great Military Display.
Tournament and <LOCATION>Ball</LOCATION>.
An Extra train will leave <LOCATION>Richmond</LOCATION> st 4 o'clock A.M., on <DATE>Wednesday</DATE>, the <DATE>4th of July</DATE>, and arrive at Jetersville in time for breakfast at the <LOCATION>Amelia Springs</LOCATION>. Passengers by this train can spend the day at the <LOCATION>Springs</LOCATION> and attend the Ball at night. Passengers going by the 7 o'clock regular train reach the <LOCATION>Springs</LOCATION> at 10:30, returning to <LOCATION>Richmond</LOCATION> by the train at 12 o'clock at night. Tickets for the round trip. $2.
je 30'-5t
<PERSON>R.E. Hughson</PERSON>, Ticket Agent